https://pbn.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy of Providence Business News
Providence Business News collects some Personal Data from its Users.
Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:
Advertising
AdvertServe
Analytics
Google Analytics, Wordpress Stats, Facebook Ads conversion tracking (Facebook pixel) and SumoMe Content Analytics
Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data
Displaying content from external platforms
Google Fonts
Personal Data: Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
YouTube video widget
Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data
Handling payments
Stripe and Authorize.Net
Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
ActiveCampaign
Personal Data: Cookies; email address; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
Further information about Personal Data
Selling goods and services online
The Personal Data collected are used to provide the User with services or to sell goods, including payment and possible delivery.
The Personal Data collected to complete the payment may include the credit card, the bank account used for the transfer, or any other means of payment envisaged. The kind of Data collected by Providence Business News depends on the payment system used.
Push notifications
Providence Business News may send push notifications to the User to achieve the purposes outlined in this privacy policy.
Users may in most cases opt-out of receiving push notifications by visiting their device settings, such as the notification settings for mobile phones, and then change those settings for Providence Business News, some or all of the apps on the particular device.
Users must be aware that disabling push notifications may negatively affect the utility of Providence Business News.
iubenda hosts this content and only collects the Personal Data strictly necessary for it to be provided.
Show the complete Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy generated with
Generate yours
